And to you, good day.
>> My name is Yona.
>> If you say so.
>> I married 40 years. I have seven
children.
>> Oh, all right.
>> And uh
I raised them all these years, take care
of the household
and my baby is 21 now and it's time for
me and I have a question.
>> Yes.
>> I'm a makeup artist and I'm a real
estate agent.
>> Yes. And I'm planning of opening in back
of my house a restaurant only three time
a day. Yemenite food.
>> All right.
>> For three hour a day.
>> All right. This is part of your passion.
Yes.
>> Yes. And I am confused. I'm ask I wanted
to know on which field should I go?
Makeup artist. Um the restaurant.
>> Why do you only have to do one?
>> Why do I have what?
>> Why do you only have to choose one? If
they're all expressions of your passion,
>> don't you understand again that the
organizing principle of synchronicity
will organize them in a way to know in
which order to do them? And maybe you
can even do more than one at a time. But
let synchronicity show you.
It will show you what you need to do
first, second, third. It will show you.
>> I'm still waiting for it to show me for
the last.
>> You have to start taking action on
something for it to show you. You have
to take action somewhere. Look, if you
have several things that seem equally
passionate, they're not always equally
able to be acted on. Are they all
equally able to be acted on? Can you
start all of them equally or is one more
able to be acted on?
>> It's depend. It's not up to me. If I
will get the job, I will do. Yeah. All
of them.
>> All right. So, as we say, if they all
seem equally exciting
>> and they all seem equally capable of
being acted on, flip a coin
>> and [clears throat] see which comes up.
All right, A, maybe you need a
three-sided coin. B, C, whatever. The
thing is, one of two things will happen
if you say, "All right, A, I'll do this,
heads, I'll do that. Tails, I'll do
that. And maybe something else. If the
coin lands on its side, I'll do that."
But the idea is the first thing that
might happen when you flip the coin,
maybe it'll say A and you'll go, "Oh, I
really wanted it to say B." Now you know
which one has more passion in it. If
that doesn't happen and it still seems
all equal, then it doesn't matter which
one you start first. It's up to you to
make that decision. Because again, if
it's not the path that you need to start
first, synchronicity as the organizing
principle will turn you around to the
path you actually need to start first.
It's the true organizing principle. It
will show you what you need to do and
what you don't need to do. So start
anything and the situations will evolve
to let you know whether keep going
>> or turn around and do something else.
>> Oh, okay. It will show you. Remember I
said it's a self-guiding system. That's
what we mean. It will guide you. It
leaves nothing out including this is the
path over here. Not this one. This path.
Start this one first. It will guide you.
But you have to take action on something
in order to find out whether to keep
going on it or get turned around to
something else. It will show you. Does
that help?
>> I see. Thank you.
>> You're welcome.
>> Question number two.
>> Yes. Um, I get almost every day or the
other day I see 1111 1111.
>> Yes. Yes. Yes. Those synchronicity
numbers let you know that when you see
those synchronistic numbers, you're
saying you're in the correct state right
now. Act from that state because those
are like road signs. They're like road
markers. Right now, you are in alignment
with your true self. You're on the right
path. Act from that state. That's what
it feels like. Bang. At that moment,
this is what you really feel like.
That's what the number is reflecting to
you as a synchronistic marker.
>> Mhm.
>> Yes.
>> Thank you very much.
>> Yes. You're welcome.
>> Appreciate it.
[applause]
>> Hi Bashar.
>> Andy you. Good day.
>> So my first question is for as long as I
can remember even before I found your
work.
>> Yes. Every time I look up at the night
sky, I look right at Orion.
>> Oh, all right.
>> What does that mean?
>> It means you have strong connections to
the different histories and pathways of
experience in the old Orion systems that
you are now utilizing and drawing from
on Earth to transform darkness into
light.
>> Okay, that resonates.
>> Thank you.
>> Do I have hybrid children?
>> Yes.
>> How many? Well, again, when we answer
that question, it depends upon the
amount of genetic material that is in
them above a certain percentage that
would make them yours. Because the idea
is that genetic material is spread among
thousands of hybrids. But in general,
more than 15% of your genetic material
usually only exists somewhere between 15
to 17, maybe sometimes as high as 23.
>> Wow.
>> So, I'm an acupuncturist.
>> All right.
>> And
>> was that a question?
>> No.
>> All right. And [laughter] um I nobody
really knows where it came from, who who
or what discovered it. Do you have any
information you can share?
>> It was understood in what you call
Atlantean times.
>> Oh wow.
>> It was developed back then.
>> How long ago was that?
>> About 20,000 of your years ago.
>> Wow. Okay. Now, it doesn't mean that
humans didn't understand that there were
certain energy meridians on the body
before that. We're answering your
specific question of when the idea of
acupuncture was developed to take
advantage of the knowledge of those
particular energy meridians in the body.
>> Okay. And so, but but um societies have
been aware of the meridians. Yes.
>> For even longer.
>> Yes. Most likely around a 100,000 years
or so
>> because the meridians contain light and
electricity,
>> magnetism, all of that. Yes. Yes.
>> Okay.
>> Um is astrology real
>> as a permission slip? Remember
permission slips is any tool, any
technique, any ritual, any object that
allows you by using it to give yourself
permission to be more of who you are. So
it's a reflection. It's not a causation.
No permission slip is a causation of
anything. It's a reflection of the state
of your consciousness to help guide you
if you are prone to gravitate to that
particular permission slip because it
aligns with your belief system.
>> Okay. In terms of financial abundance
does
>> watch it
>> remember what we've already said about
abundance. Yes.
>> Okay.
>> Before you continue that question, did
you understand what we already said?
>> Yes. Are you going to still ask the
question?
>> Yes.
>> All right.
>> Okay. [laughter]
>> Does saving money energetically
represent fear of lack of it?
>> It depends on the person and why they're
doing it, doesn't it? Remember when we
said anything can be used positively or
negatively?
>> Yes,
>> anything. So, the idea of saving money
can be a positive act. It can be a
negative act.
>> It just depends on how you feel about
it.
>> It depends on your belief system as to
why you're doing it.
>> Okay. The feeling may come as a result
of the belief system and give you a clue
as to why you're doing it and whether
it's positive or negative. So you can
use the feeling that you associate with
it to determine whether you are doing it
positively or negatively.
>> Yes.
>> All right. Does that help?
>> Yes. And last last question. I have
really bad insomnia.
>> You mean really good insomnia?
>> Yeah. I'm really good.
>> If you have bad insomnia, you're
sleeping.
>> That's true. I'm really good at staying
awake.
>> All right.
>> What is What is that about? I
>> Well, it depends. It could be many
different things.
>> Okay.
>> We sense from you that you're waiting
for some kind of a connection at night,
but you're not exactly sure you want to
go through the experience that the
connection will bring
>> a connection with
>> some different extradimensional sources,
extraterrestrial sources. Oh,
>> so you're kind of staying awake because
in one sense you kind of want to be
around when it happens. You don't want
to necessarily be unconscious for it,
>> but at the same time you are also not
willing to let go to get into the state
where it's most probable that it will
happen. So you're kind of between what
you typically refer to as humans as a
rock and a hard place. You're kind of
putting yourself in a neutral state
because you kind of want it to happen
this way and don't really want it to
happen this way, but you do want it to
happen knowing that it will most likely
happen this way, but you'd rather it
happen this way.
Is that making some sense
>> a little?
>> All right. So, what we would suggest is
this.
>> Okay.
When you lie down in bed,
just take a few deep breaths and allow
yourself to relax into the idea of
letting the connection happen in the way
that actually serves everyone best. Just
let it happen that way and allow
yourself to get used to the idea that it
may change over time and you may become
more aware of it in different ways. But
let yourself relax into the idea that
whatever connections are going to happen
are going to happen for the best
possible reasons to serve you and
everyone involved. And just see if you
can relax into that understanding. And
once you can allow yourself to relax and
you feel yourself starting to drift,
allow yourself to ask, just ask that it
happen in a way that allows you more
conscious awareness of what's going on
and that you know you will be fine if
that is given.
>> Okay.
>> All right. Now, do you have a particular
affinity for a particular spirit guide?
>> No. Are you sure?
>> What's an example?
>> Do you have an attraction to a
particular
thing, a flower, a tree, a name, an idea
that you don't really know why you're
attracted to it, but you are attracted
to it. It just sort of pops in now and
then.
>> Butterfly.
>> All right. Is that a question or a
statement?
>> It's a statement.
>> All right. How often do you find that
that happens?
>> That I find that what happens? that you
think of butterflies?
>> Um,
>> did you answer the question we asked? We
said, "Do you have something that just
pops in? You don't know why."
>> Oh, no. I'm just always drawn to
butterflies.
>> All right. All right. Good enough. Good
enough. Then we would suggest that when
you lie down and let yourself relax and
start to drift, you think of
butterflies.
>> Okay? that will help you make a bridge
and a link to the vibration of a
different reality that will allow you to
relax into it and get used to it so that
you can have more conscious awareness of
what's going on. And let yourself go
into that third [snorts] state, that
alternate reality state between what you
consider to be physical reality and what
you consider to be non-physical reality
or spirit. So that you can experience
the connections that you really do wish
to experience more consciously.
Okay.
>> All right.
>> Great.
>> So, butterflies,
any particular color?
>> No.
>> Are you sure?
>> Yes.
>> All right. Then don't be surprised if a
particular color stands out and becomes
your symbol.
>> Okay.
>> All right.
Pleasant dreams.
And and and one other thing
>> we gave the suggestion to someone else
who brought up this subject.
>> How's the humor in your life?
>> It's good. It's abundant.
>> Is it?
>> Yeah.
>> You laugh a lot?
>> I do.
>> All right. We would suggest that as you
lie down, you think of things that make
you laugh.
>> Okay.
>> It will help you let go.
>> All right. That's very helpful. Thank
you.
>> You're welcome. [applause]
[applause]
>> And you good day.
Speak up. Speak up so that all may hear
what you have to share.
>> Okay. So, a couple weeks ago, I had a
dream where I looked up and saw a bunch
of spaceships.
>> Yes.
>> And one
>> I sometimes have that without being
asleep because I don't sleep anymore.
>> That's awesome. So, one came down to me
and the being that came out, I ran up
and gave him a big hug and I was crying
and sobbing and it felt like I really
had missed him.
>> Yes.
>> And I'm wondering uh so I've connected
with him through meditation.
>> Yes.
>> Um since I'm wondering if you can tell
me what race he is.
>> You're dealing with another hybrid race
primarily what we would label the Yel.
>> Okay. In any such encounters that are
going on between you and
extraterrestrial beings, you will
usually find that you will have at least
one counterpart in that society that
will be involved in the encounters so
that they feel familiar and are a
reflection of more of you. So in a
sense, it's like meeting another version
of yourself.
>> Okay. So he is my counterpart.
>> Yes.
>> Awesome. Um, so in the dream I got on a
ship and went out to space and saw the
earth get really swallow. So was that
physical or was it
>> Well, yes and no. You have to understand
that many of these encounters actually
happen in a slightly shifted version of
physical reality that allows you to
experience more than you otherwise might
in your typical physical reality. So
yes, it was physically real but not in
your physical dimension. Exactly.
>> Okay. Uh, do I have hybrid children?
>> Yes.
>> How many have a significant amount of my
DNA?
>> Again, the average is usually about 15
to 17.
>> Okay. So, you've mentioned the
possibility of hybrid children living on
Earth as soon as 2022. Is that still
>> No, no, no.
>> No. Okay.
>> I said the window of open contact is
between 2025, 2033, maybe 2040. I did
not say the hybrid children will be
landing at the beginning. Somewhere in
there, things will be set up so that
they can begin to stay longer and longer
and longer on your planet in certain
areas that are sequestered and safe for
them to acclimate and adapt to your
society as your society acclimates to
them. But the idea is that some of them
have been on your planet and do come to
your world from time to time in secret
places that are set aside for them so
they can practice what it's like being
on Earth because many things that you
take for granted are very alien to them.
So they have to learn the idea of how to
fit into your society to some degree,
although they won't go all the way with
it because human society must also adapt
to them to some degree as well. But
they're willing to learn and they're
quite fascinated by some things that you
don't even really think about. Like
eating food off a plate with a fork.
Why?
Why not just take the food and put it in
your mouth with your hand? [laughter]
So they have a lot of things to sort of
learn to fit in a little bit. But they
do that on your planet from time to time
in houses and apartments that you don't
necessarily even know that they happen
to be in. that might even be right next
door.
>> Wow. [snorts] Okay. So, I wanted to talk
about being a bridge to the higher
dimensions. Um, so when I'm meditating
and I can converse and see in my mind,
my hybrid children.
>> Yes.
>> Uh, what reality is that? And what does
that look like on their end for? Well,
again, you're communicating through that
slightly altered reality that we just
mentioned, and therefore they're
receiving it in a sense, sort of
telepathically, from you.
>> Okay. Um, so is it helpful or important
to be making these emotional and like
relationship connections with them?
>> Is it helpful and important to you?
>> Yes.
>> Well, then the answer is yes.
>> Okay? because they will feel the
importance to you and that will allow
them to begin to identify and empathize
with those feelings and understand them
more clearly.
>> Okay. Um so earlier this week I had a
really powerful meditation where I felt
like I was speaking with you and was
that really you or was it just
>> you're just tapping into the vibration
uh that you recognize as our collective
consciousness through your own higher
mind. So what you were doing, which is
what you're doing right now, was
speaking a little bit more clearly to
your own higher mind, using us as a
filter or a mask to do so.
>> Okay. And what is my vibration?
>> Are you sure you want to know? Because
remember, as soon as you ask, it goes
down.
>> Um, well, mostly my question was, I've
really been meditating a lot and it's
felt really good. It's been
>> All right, that's fine.
>> Passion.
>> But are you taking actions as well?
>> Yes.
>> All right. Because remember that's the
language of physical reality.
>> Okay?
>> Not just meditating. You have to act to
be in the world. So do your meditations
help you take more actions in the
direction of your passion.
>> Yes.
>> All right. Are you sure? Didn't sound
very convincing.
>> I've I've been taking a lot of action
the last year and it's felt like I've
been really just outside and not really
going inside and so it's I've been
feeling really called.
>> All right. You can balance it out.
That's
>> Yeah, I am excited to take more action
soon.
>> All right. Thank you.
>> Thank you.
[applause]
>> Thank you, beloved Bashar.
>> And good day to you.
>> Good day to you.
>> Speak up, please.
>> Okay. Um I've been listening to you um
many years ago and I'm very grateful to
be here.
>> All right. Um I've been doing a lot of
work uh inwardly for for self to grow
and um you know to become more of who I
am.
>> Yes.
>> And I creating a secret of meditation
in my house with um people that coming
over.
>> All right. And I I do believe with the
water and air and uh all the seven
things that you've been uh provide
tonight. Uh the thing is that I've been
asking is about my son that he he's back
in my house and he doesn't he stay all
night with the the heater and he doesn't
really drink enough water and um I if
you have a way for me to um
>> What are you asking? Should you tie him
down and force me?
>> No. Well,
>> uh, just that, um,
>> have you had conversations about why and
does he actually feel like he's not
getting enough?
>> He would listen to others, but not to
his parents, I guess.
>> Have you had a conversation about why he
doesn't listen to your advice?
>> Usually kids don't listen to their
parents.
>> That's not the case on my planet.
>> I know, but here it's a little bit
different. Well, I understand that. But
do you also understand he may have his
own path in life?
>> I I totally agree with you.
>> All right.
>> The thing is that um like you said, uh
>> I have a suggestion for you.
>> Okay. Thank you.
>> Let's call it the Santa Claus effect.
>> Yes.
>> Leave a picture of water and a glass out
for him when you go to bed. Maybe in the
night he will sneak over and have some
water without you necessarily knowing
about it.
>> Okay. Thank you.
>> Yes.
>> Just give him the option. Don't tell him
what to do.
>> No, I And you absolutely right. I do
that. I just put
>> But do you leave water out?
>> Yes, I do put water
>> when you're not around.
>> When I'm not around?
>> Yes. When you go to bed?
>> Yeah.
>> Leave water out. Okay. Okay.
>> So that you're not around. So that he
can have it when you're not around.
>> Okay.
>> You understand?
>> Yes.
>> All right.
>> Yes. And for the for the heater that is
whole night long and there's no air in
this room, no windows open, nothing.
>> Is he cold?
>> He always said that he's cold.
>> All right.
>> But then there's no air at all for all.
>> There must be some or he would
suffocate. [laughter] Remember that's
the first basic need. And without air,
you'll probably be dead in about 2
minutes.
>> Yeah. But I can see that he has like the
eyes swollen. I can see he's very
fatigued and
>> All right. Well, have you had a
conversation about the fact as to
whether or not he enjoys that feeling?
>> I do, but as I said that he doesn't
listen to
>> I didn't say that you had to say
something he had to listen to. I said,
have you had a conversation about
whether or not he enjoys that effect?
>> If he's enjoying that, um,
>> yes, ask him. Look, your eyes are kind
of puffy and swollen and so on and so
forth and you seem very tired. Do you
enjoy that feeling? I'm just curious.
>> Okay, I will ask him that.
>> Sure.
>> Then it's not about him listening to
you. It's about you paying attention and
giving him options to respond in the way
that he prefers to respond.
>> Okay. [clears throat]
>> Yes.
>> All right. And again, he doesn't have to
answer. Just pose the question. He'll go
through it in his mind and maybe he'll
decide that he needs to make different
choices to have different consequences.
But you're being the one that's
imaginative enough to simply get the
ball rolling in his own mind without
making him think he has to listen to
you.
>> Mhm.
>> Do you understand?
>> Yes.
>> All right. You need to be a little bit
more imaginative and we don't mean this
in a negative way, a little bit more
sneaky. [clears throat] Oh,
>> so that you can inspire him to think
about things without him feeling that he
is being told what to do.
>> Okay?
>> Do you understand?
>> Thank you. [clears throat]
>> You just have to exercise your
curiosity. Because again, if that really
is his path, if that's something he
believes he needs to do, then the only
thing coming from you in your
unconditional love and support is,
"Well, I'm curious. Do you find that
sensation interesting or enjoyable or
let me know? I'm kind of curious
and then walk away. You don't even have
to finish the conversation.
[laughter]
>> Thank you very very much, Bashar.
>> You're very very welcome.
>> There's anything else that do you see
from what I I do for self doing work?
Can
>> are you acting on your passion to the
best you can with no insistence or
assumption on the outcome and remaining
in a positive state no matter what
manifests?
>> Yes.
>> Don't lie. [laughter]
>> I didn't hear the whole question but I
understand.
>> All right then. That's just my curious
question. [laughter]
>> So you can go think about it.
>> I will. [laughter]
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you very very much Bashar. Vishar,
I'm interested in the technology
raw mentioned in the raw material
known as the prana vacuum. How can we
create
a
prana vacuum
using today's technology?
The so-called prana vacuum is the same
thing as the idea of what you might call
the quantum vacuum. Is the same thing as
the zero point energy concept that many
people are talking about on your planet.
It exists all around you. The technology
exists that you can use to tap into it
in certain ways. Many of the kinds of
things that people have invented that
say it's tapping into the zero point
energy are not exactly doing so. But the
idea is growing in the consciousness,
the collective consciousness of your
planet until such time as that awareness
evolves into technology that will truly
tap into that prana field, the quantum
field, the void, and whatever else you
may wish to call it. It will allow you
unlimited energy, unlimited flow, and
inexhaustible supply of energy that can
be utilized in a variety of ways once
you truly tap into that technology. It
has to do with creating devices of
proper resonance, proper frequencies,
capacitors that vibrate at certain
resonant frequencies that deliver and
transform energy in a certain way. Step
it down in a way that you can use with
your technology. We have talked a little
bit about this as a space-time antenna
concept. Three nested spheres separated
by fi ratio diameters penetrated by
antenni that are insulated from a merka,
a double interpenetrated tetrahedrin in
the center of the three spheres that
resonates at certain frequencies and can
be activated by the introduction of
energy into it and it will output energy
of a higher caliber, a higher level and
a higher frequency tapping into the
quantum field in certain ways. But many
people on your planet, a few of them are
beginning to experiment with this and we
cannot deliver more information about
this device until they have already
achieved what it is we have already
delivered. End of discussion.
>> Hello Bashar.
>> Good day.
>> Uh thank you for having this
conversation with each other in this
way.
>> It is our passion and our pleasure to do
so. What would you like to discuss?
>> Talking about the hybrid children. Um
you've mentioned in the past that
contact between hybrid children and
their mothers will expand over time.
>> Yes.
>> Has this process indeed started on this
timeline? Is there is there an increase
of physical contact between human beings
and the hybrid children?
>> Yes, but in an altered reality, not
necessarily physically on your planet so
much, but in a slightly altered version
of physical reality. And in dream time,
these encounters have increased.
>> Okay. Wonderful.
>> Eventually, it will leak into the
physical reality as you understand it.
>> Although it will still be of a higher
vibration than it is now.
>> Yes, understand. Yeah. And um I also
wanted to talk to you about suppressed
memories.
>> Yes.
>> During our previous conversation, you've
mentioned that I was visited by the
grace when I also was a child.
>> Yes. And that these experiences are
buried deep within my consciousness.
>> Well, not that deep.
>> Oh, not that deep. [laughter]
You also mentioned that I felt
victimized because my childlike state
was not able to comprehend what was
going on during these visitations.
>> Yes.
>> Okay. And is it correct to say that from
the point of view as a human being child
that these visitations and the removal
of genetic material was somehow
experienced as a trauma on a
psychological level?
>> Yes. But only because of the way you
were raised as a human. Not because it's
innate to the being a child. Not because
it's innate to being a human child. just
because of the way your planet views
these kinds of things and because it is
shortsighted in its compartmentalization
of awareness. That's the only reason you
experienced it traumatically.
>> And is that also the reason that we're
still somehow afraid of
extraterrestrials?
>> Because you are afraid of portions of
your own power and the extraterrestrials
you're encountering represent and
reflect the idea of your true power in
certain ways. Uh I understand and that
yeah that's probably not a coincidence
but that leads up to my next question.
Um
both my parents have transitioned almost
within 3 years of each other and the
last parent my father passed one year
ago.
>> Yes.
>> And their physical absence caused a
shift in my life.
>> Yes. Of course that's the purpose of it.
>> Yeah. [laughter]
Um, I experienced this as a tremendous
opportunity to shed a whole bunch of
negative belief systems that I have
bestowed upon myself through their
upbringing.
>> Well, congratulations. That is a
positive way to use it.
>> Thank you. But I also sense that this
tremendous opportunity is sometimes a
bit frightening.
>> Why?
>> As if this whole new space that has
opened up is sometimes too big to
handle.
>> Impossible. Otherwise, you wouldn't
experience it.
You only grow into the space you're
ready for. So no matter how it looks,
you're making a comparison, still using
some of the outdated beliefs to view it
instead of letting go of those outdated
beliefs and understanding you cannot
experience more than you're ready for
anyway.
You can expand into it. That's why it
looks that big because that's how big
you actually are when you let go of the
limiting beliefs.
>> Mhm. I understand what you're saying.
>> I understand what you're saying.
>> And I also um am aware of the physical
impact of this awareness.
>> Yes.
>> Uh uh for instance, when my body is
sleeping,
>> Yes.
>> it seems to respond to this awareness
with an actual physical shock during the
night that eventually wakes me up.
>> Yes, it can. Because again your body is
not used to the vibration or frequency
of energy but it can get used to it over
time.
>> And how how how can we do that? Can you
say something about um how to to
integrate this new space and the
awareness of new space and the physical
response to this? Is it just going with
the flow letting it happen? That
>> that's one way practice in a sense
having it happen over and over again.
You'll get used to it. That's one way.
But one way to accelerate that is to
understand or have a perspective
where physical reality isn't really
separate from spirit reality. It's
really not so different. It's just that
you've defined it as very different.
You've placed certain definitions on
physical reality that makes it seem so
unlike spirit reality when in fact it's
a natural extension of it.
>> Okay. and the and the and the and the
physical body that reacts. Um um how can
we smoothen that out? Well, this is what
I'm telling you. Stop making such a
separation in your belief system between
the idea of your physical body and your
spirit. Your physical body is your
spirit in physical terms. Mhm.
>> It's the same kind of idea, if you wish,
a crude analogy of saying
ice is still water. It's just frozen,
>> but it's the same thing. It's the same
substance essentially, and so is steam.
So if you start looking at your body as
if it's simply euphemistically a frozen
version of your spirit or at least a
portion of your spirit, you can start to
allow the physical reality to sort of
melt a little bit more,
>> allow it to become a little bit more
fluid, a little bit more liquid and not
be so different from the liquid version
or the steam version. So you have to
start really looking at physical reality
as if it's just another state of being
of spirit and not really separate. It's
the idea of separation that's tripping
you up.
>> Yeah, I understand. Understand.
>> And um
you also said something about um that
the human beings on earth will become
more and more human over time. Yes.
You're actually not fully human yet.
>> Yeah. And I was wondering what you meant
by that. What does it mean to be human
as opposed to not being fully human?
>> Being fully human means that you
understand that everything is made of
unconditional love. You understand that
everything is connected. Everything is a
reflection of everything else and you
act accordingly.
>> Mhm.
Yes. Being fully human is what you
ascribe to beings like Christ, Buddha,
Krishna, so on and so forth. It's the
idea of the behavior that reflects the
godhood within you.
>> Yes.
Yeah. And that probably also means that
um we're not so compartmentalized in our
way of thinking then.
>> Exactly. You think more holistically,
more as a whole system. That's why I
said you understand everything is one
thing. I am you from another point of
view. Literally, I am you from another
point of view. You are us from another
point of view. A fully realized human
lives
in that truth.
>> Yeah. Thank you so much, Bashar.
>> You are so welcome. Ao.
>> Ao.
Greetings Bashar. I have a question for
you. What is the template level of our
space-time reality? You've mentioned
that there is a template level and that
we are each exploring themes
from this template level that there is a
specific template for our lives. I'm
wondering if this template is actually
revealed in the deck of what we consider
52 playing cards. And if this template
level of reality is expressed,
symbolized in the deck of 52 playing
cards, where exactly did these cards
come from? Who created them and when?
And what is the best way for us to
utilize these cards now in our lives in
order to explore the theme of our lives?
play our cards right and give ourselves
permission to be our best self. Thanks
Bashar.
>> All 52 are symbolic of the template
level because it can be mixed and
matched in any number of ways. It's not
any one card. It's all of them that
represents and symbolizes the template
level which is created by the choices
you make in spirit to have a physical
experience. So as above so below. You
use the energy of the consciousness
field to arrange
certain kinds of blueprints that will
manifest physiologically as the theme
you will explore in physical reality.
And the idea of any kind of permission
slip like a normal deck of cards or
tarot cards or any kind of divination
system represents to some degree the
idea of the template level. Now you have
some freedom in that with your free will
as to how you experience the template
you laid out for yourself. And sometimes
some things can be altered or shifted.
But in general, the choices made by you
as a spirit will be played out as the
cards you are dealt. But you can shift
them around a little bit here and there
with your free will. But you will play
that game. That's what you decided as a
spirit. So that's how the cards
represent the idea of the template level
in energy that then becomes crystallized
down in frequency down into what you
experience as the physical card game
that you are playing. Playing the right
cards as you say is easy when you simply
follow the formula. That's the secret to
playing your best hand.
>> Hey, how are you?
>> Perfect. And you?
>> Yeah, I'm fine. Uh let's see. My
questions are
um are feelings or thoughts the higher
priority for manifesting our reality?
Because it seems like
uh unresolved feelings manifest over our
thoughts. So how are they linked? And
this is how it works. First you begin
with beliefs and definitions. What you
believe to be true is reinforced by the
idea of feeling that it is true,
thinking that it is true, and behaving
as if it is true. Belief systems use
feelings, emotions, thoughts, and
behaviors to reinforce the validity and
the reality of the belief system because
physical reality isn't really real.
Therefore, beliefs have to make you
believe that it is real. And they do so
by reinforcing what you believe to be
true with the idea that it feels true.
You think it's true and you behave as if
it's true. That's the priority. That's
the order in which it happens. You
cannot have a behavior. You cannot have
a thought and you cannot have an emotion
without first believing or defining that
something is true for you. Beliefs are
the blueprint that allow you to build
the house of your physical reality. So
it all starts with that. So when you
behave a certain way, when you think
certain thoughts, when you feel certain
emotions, they all go back to what must
I believe to be true about myself in
order to feel, think, and behave this
way. Does that help you?
>> Yeah. So if I want to change the belief
system, uh the action or how I behave
would be the best way to start and then
the feelings and thoughts.
>> You can start from any direction you
wish. But in a sense, the most efficient
way to change a belief system is to
figure out what that belief is telling
you. Figure out why you're buying into
it because it may simply be a habit that
you have because you've been taught to
believe this way. It may be that you're
getting something out of believing that
way because you don't hold on to any
belief you don't think serves you. So
even if it doesn't seem to serve you,
you may have a belief that says that the
alternative would be worse than holding
on to the beliefs you have even if
they're not comfortable because you all
want to believe that everything needs to
serve you, which is true. It can. But
sometimes you have beliefs and you hold
on to them even if you know they're not
the best beliefs to hold on to because
you have a belief that the alternative
would be worse. And therefore, you'll
still hold on to whatever it is you're
holding on to until you change until you
understand that the idea that something
worse will happen if you behave more
like your true self is a fallacy. So you
have to examine why the belief is there
to begin with. Allow yourself to
understand why you're buying into it and
be honest in your self-investigation of
what you believe will happen if you
actually go in a direction you say you
would prefer to. Once you understand
that a negative and fear-based belief is
simply telling you a story that isn't
necessarily true, then you can see that
it is nonsensical and illogical. And as
soon as it is nonsensical, you will drop
it because you don't hold on to things
that don't make sense. If you do hold on
to things that don't make sense, it's
because you have a belief that says it
makes more sense than the alternative.
>> This is what we call the motivational
mechanism in your psychology as humans.
You always always without fail
move in the direction of what you
believe serves you. You always without
fail move away from what you believe
does not serve you. So if you see
yourself choosing things that you know
intellectually don't serve you, it can
only mean you've defined it and attached
a belief to it that says it's better
than the alternative. It serves you
better than the alternative. Find out
why you believe that. And when you
expose the belief and the story it's
telling you, you will see that it makes
no sense and it will be dropped. It will
be gone.
>> Okay. Thank you.
>> Yes.
Uh
>> [clears throat]
>> um
let's see uh the next question is uh
from the soul's perspective
um is the physical body like a
radiocontrolled car where you uh the
soul uh puts inputs to make it go left
and right and then there's always input
also input from the environment. So it's
like uh
>> to some degree you can use whatever
analogy you wish
>> but the idea really is that the physical
world and the physical body is a
projection of the soul's consciousness.
It's like putting on a diving suit. More
than the idea of a remote control car.
It's like putting on a diving suit or a
diving mask and going diving under the
ocean. The mask helps you see underneath
the ocean clearly.
It's not designed to tell you what to
do. It's designed to tell you what
you're experiencing more clearly. When
you leave the physical reality, it's
like taking off the diving mask and
going back to the surface.
So even though you have free will as a
physical being, the soul determines what
the general trajectory is from its own
free will. And that may be what the
physical mind thinks of as destiny. In
other words, you are the person you are.
You will do everything as the person you
are. You cannot actually fundamentally
change the person that you are. Although
the personality can shift to a great
degree, but it's still happening to you
as you think of yourself as a separate
autonomous being. So you have the free
will to experience the destiny of the
soul in any way, shape or form that the
physical mind chooses to. positive,
negative, happy, sad, whatever, fast,
slow, up, down, but you will walk that
path because it was determined by your
free will as a soul. Is this helping?
>> Yeah, the diving suit uh was a much
better uh metaphor than the radio
control car.
>> All right,
>> thank you.
>> Um, two more questions really fast. Uh,
>> yes. who um when uh when a soul wants to
have an experience here on earth and
many souls wants to have an experience
here on earth uh who gets gets priority?
>> There is no need for priority because
there are a multitude of infinite
parallel realities that can have a
similar experience.
>> Uhhuh.
Okay. And then the last question, uh, on
your planet, uh, do you fart and do you
laugh at your own farts like humans do?
[laughter]
>> We laugh, but we don't eat, so we don't
fart.
>> Okay. Okay. Yeah. Uh, I think that was
all. Thank you.
>> Thank you, Ao.
>> Ao,
[sighs]
good day, Bashar. I would like to know
about the Bosnian pyramids, the ones
located in Visoko.
Uh, and like who built them and for what
purpose? And um, yeah, anything you can
tell me about
the pyramids
in Visoko in Bosnia.
Thank you.
pyramids around your planet at a certain
time were all built relatively close to
one another in time around your 10,500
years ago.
The idea is that they were energy
collectors to balance the earth that had
gone through a catastrophic change when
it was impacted by a cometary body that
caused the annihilation of your
Atlantean civilization.
And therefore knowledge and energy was
preserved in many pyramids around the
planet and also they were used as an
energy balancing system to bring the
planet back into alignment so it could
recuperate and heal. There are other
things that they were used for but we
will not go into that right now.
>> Hello
>> and to you. Good day.
>> I'm very excited to be here. Thank you
for for talking to me.
>> It is our passion and our pleasure. What
would you like to discuss? Um, so I've
been I've been following my excitement
more and more since I kind of started to
listen to to you speak and I've it feels
really great and I I've been doing some
like bigger and some smaller changes and
I'm I'm following your advice of this
thing of basically following my
excitement more moment to moment because
there's no like one big thing in that
sense.
>> All right. Now do remember the entire
formula not just follow your excitement.
There's other pieces to it. Yes. Yes.
Yes, I know.
>> All right.
>> Um and I um I think what I'm like one
thing that just as an as an example that
I I was I quit one one job that I I felt
like I was not excited about at all.
>> Um and now I have more free time which
is fun. Um, and then sometimes I
I I get kind of frustrated with myself
because I I feel like I sit there and I
have I know that I have all these
options to to act on, but I don't I kind
of don't know what to do. And I wonder,
>> yes, you do. Yes, you do. Yes, you do.
Yes, you do. The idea again isn't that
complicated. Don't over complicate it.
If you have different options, decide
for yourself which one is not only more
attractive, more exciting than any other
option, but which one can you act on,
which one can you do something about. If
it seems that more than one is equal,
you might as well flip a coin. Remember,
synchronicity comes to bear in this.
Because if you flip a coin and say, "All
right, heads option A, tails option B."
And you flip the coin, one of two things
might happen. Let's say it lands on
tails, option B, and you find yourself
going, "Oh, goody." Or you find yourself
going, "Oh, I wish it had been option A
instead. Oh, I wish it had been option
A." Then you will know that that was the
one that was more exciting. or if you do
head down a path that isn't necessarily
the most exciting path for you at that
moment, synchronicity will create
certain circumstances that will turn you
around in the correct direction. That's
how it works. It's an automatic
mechanism. So, you don't have to sit
there and wonder and wonder and be
frustrated. Just act on whatever you are
capable of acting on that contains more
excitement than anything else as far as
you can determine. And let synchronicity
guide you with the red light green light
aspect of its being of its nature which
means it will bring you opportunities
you can act on and take further green
light synchronicity. It will prevent you
from acting on certain things that are
not the correct path for you right now.
Red light synchronicity just like you
follow your traffic lights when you
drive. You understand?
>> So the starting and stopping
>> is the way synchronicity guides you. No,
not right now. Don't act in that
direction. Act in this direction.
Whatever you can act on. And you have to
use your imagination. Be very creative
about the idea of what it means to take
action on something in every way that
you possibly can that has to do with
that thing you say excites you. Even if
you have to simulate the reality, that's
taking an action on it.
Let me give you an example that many
people on your planet have used. There
are many people who you call celebrities
that are famous, but you will hear
stories from many of them that before
they were actually able to literally do
what it is that they now do that they're
famous for, they acted it out. They
simulated it. Even sometimes going so
far for someone who might be a public
speaker in an auditorium or a game show
host or a late night interviewer as to
go into a space, set it up like it's
really happening. Even to the level of
putting fake people in the audience,
maybe even just cardboard cutouts, and
doing their routine as if it's really
happening. Because then you're training
your body to get used to the vibration
of the reality of that. And that will
make you attract it more strongly by
doing anything you can to simulate
anything you can to take an action in
the direction of what excites you more
than any other choice. And when we talk
about that, it can also be very simple
things. We don't mean when we say follow
your passion, follow your excitement
that it has to be a grand project or
come with trumpets or be a lifespanning
career. Tada! Here's your passion. No.
Every day you have little options,
simple options. I can take a walk. I can
read a book. I can have lunch with a
friend. I can watch a movie.
Just choose the one that has more
attractiveness, more curiosity, more
excitement, even just the tiniest bit
more that you're able to act on than any
other one. And just do that first.
You're still following your excitement
by doing it on that level. And
eventually, it will usually snowball
through synchronicity to bring you more
and more opportunities to act on your
passion in bigger and bigger and bigger
ways. But the point is, it doesn't
really matter if it does or not because
you're still following your excitement
just by making sure that every day the
options you choose are more exciting
than any other option and taking action
on the ones that you can. That's all
there is to it. You don't have to make
it a big mystery or over complicate it
or overthink it. That's why you're
frustrated.
>> So, you're saying I'm frustrated because
I am making it way more complicated.
>> Yes.
Because I feel like sometimes it's it's
literally that I have like an afternoon
off and I'm sitting at home and I I I I
don't know like I'm I I
>> Then you're not using your creative
imagination
>> sitting at home. Why are you speaking
with us today? Was this more exciting
than any other option?
>> Yes.
>> Well, you see that wasn't hard. So, what
will you do after this conversation is
over? What are your options after this
conversation is over? What are your
options? Name some.
>> Um, probably go to sleep because it's
quite late here.
>> All right. Going to sleep can be
exciting. That's fine. But let's say
it's morning. What would be some of your
options?
>> Um, I usually like go for a walk, go to
work out. Um,
>> do you enjoy those things? Are they
expressions of your passion? Uh,
>> yes, they are.
>> Are you sure? Cuz you kind of hesitated.
>> [laughter]
>> No, I'm sure.
>> All right. Because remember, sometimes
you may be sort of doing what excites
you, but you may not be doing it in the
most exciting way. Because the idea of
following your passion requires every
component of it to also be the most
exciting way. So you can do a thing but
where you're doing it, how you're doing
it, when you're doing it, with whom
you're doing it all have to be of that
vibration or you're not really following
your passion. So you get to decide the
way in which you're actually acting on
your excitement. And isn't that an
exciting thought?
>> It is actually.
>> All right. So, just make sure that
whatever it is you choose to do out of
the options that you have, whether it's
taking a walk or working out, you're
doing it in the most exciting way as a
whole system. All the components of it
are being done in the most exciting way.
And if you can't find that one of the
components is the most exciting way you
would prefer to do it, invent, use your
creative imagination to create your
exciting way of doing it.
>> Yes.
Yeah, I think that that what you just
said with the creative Yeah, that that
actually helps a lot. I've never thought
about it that way, but I have the power
to do that.
>> You do.
>> You do. So,
>> if that makes things more exciting, then
you're on the right path.
>> Yeah.
>> Does this help?
>> Thank you. Yeah, that that helped a lot.
Yes, it really did.
>> All right. Does that serve you today?
>> Yes. [clears throat]
>> Then we thank you for your interaction,
AO. Thank you. Have a great day.
>> Of course. Always you, too.
>> Thanks. Bye.
>> Why would I have anything else?
>> Sorry.
>> Why would I choose anything else?
>> Oh, yeah. That's um makes sense.
>> Yes, I know. That's why I said it.
>> So, go see
>> and don't choose what doesn't make
sense.
>> I will. Thank you so much, Rashar.
>> It's up to you. C you.